

CONTACT

meziepage@gmail.com

+234 903 411 3966

MR. Peter Ikemma
Compound, Dusogu
Awkuzu

EDUCATION

HTML5/CSS3/JAVASCRIPT

ApTech Computer Education
2020 - 2022

React.js, Next.js, React Native, TailwindCSS, Typescript Nnamdi Azikiwe Unversity Awka 2022 - present

SKILLS

- HTML5/CSS3/Javascript/Jquery
- React.js
- Next.js
- React Native
- Tailwind/Boostrap/ChakraUI
- Typescript

LANGUAGE

English Igbo

IKEMMA AUGUSTINE

Front-End Engineer

About Me

I'm a front-end engineer specializing in HTML5, CSS3, React.js, Typescript, Next.js, TailwindCSS/Boostrap/ChakraUi, Jquery. and React Native, I excel in crafting user-friendly, responsive web and mobile applications, optimizing performance, and staying current with industry trends. Let's collaborate for exceptional user experiences

WORK EXPERIENCE

h b

Jan 2022 - present

Ventlio Inc

Senior Front-end Engineer

- User-focused design, responsive web and mobile development.
- UI/UX design, code optimization for peak performance.
- Create interfaces, develop and maintain codebase.

Jul 2021 - Aug 2022

Oltem-logistics

Senior Front-end Engineer

- Design engaging interfaces, ensure cross-browser compatibility.
- Design responsive, user-centric interfaces while maintaining clean, efficient code for optimal performance.

REFERENCES

Ezeobi Sunny

Ventlio Inc. / Front-end

Phone: +234 705 658 4464

Email: ezeobisunny51@gmail.com

Ifemezue John

Oltem-logistics / CEO

Phone: +234 703 082 2450

Email: johnifemezuoanayo@gmail.com